As a result of trade, travel and migration, different cuisines have spread across the world.
由于贸易、旅行和迁徙，不同的菜系已经传播到世界各地。
Many recipes, chefs and restaurants try to claim that their example of a particular culinary tradition is the most authentic.
许多食谱、厨师和餐馆都试图声称他们的独特烹饪传统是最正宗的。
But is this a good thing?
但这是好事吗？
People care about authenticity because food traditions are closely linked to identity, particularly for migrant communities.
人们关心正宗，因为食物传统与身份认同密切相关，尤其是对于移民社区而言。
Sociologist and professor of food studies, Krishnendu Ray, explains that home cooking is often the last way that communities can show their identity.
社会学家兼食品研究教授克里希南杜·雷伊解释说，家常菜往往是社区展示其身份的最后方式。
British celebrity chef Jamie Oliver was accused of trying to take advantage of positive feelings about Jamaica.
英国名厨杰米·奥利弗被指责试图利用人们对牙买加的好感。
His ready meal product had a Jamaican name, but was unlike genuine Jamaican cooking.
他的即食餐产品有一个牙买加名字，但不像真正的牙买加菜。
However, food consultant Sara Kay asks whether there are problems with the idea of authenticity.
然而，食品顾问萨拉·凯质疑正宗性这一概念本身是否有问题。
She highlights that these ideas often come from the expectations that majority cultures have about minority cultures and their food.
她强调，这些想法往往来自主流文化对少数族裔文化及其食物的期望。
These can be restricting – restauranteurs have complained that people expect Asian food to be cheaper than that from European cultures.
这些期望可能是限制性的——餐馆老板抱怨说，人们期望亚洲食物比欧洲文化的食物更便宜。
Expectations can also give people a false idea of what is authentic.
期望也可能给人们带来关于什么是正宗的错误观念。
While large cities are full of eateries representing different countries – China, India, Italy, Mexico and more – these labels can oversimplify the reality of food from these countries.
虽然大城市里遍布着代表不同国家——中国、印度、意大利、墨西哥等等——的餐馆，但这些标签可能过度简化了这些国家食物的现实情况。
Stephanie Elizondo Greist was surprised by the difference between regional specialities in different parts of Mexico and what she ate growing up as a Mexican-American in Texas, but feels that both are authentic examples of Mexican food.
斯蒂芬妮·埃利松多·格雷斯特对墨西哥不同地区的特色菜与她作为墨西哥裔美国人在得克萨斯州长大时所吃的食物之间的差异感到惊讶，但她认为两者都是正宗的墨西哥食物。
A more controversial view of authenticity was stated by American Chef Andrew Zimmern, who claimed that he could bring Chinese dishes to Minnesota in a more authentic way than existing restaurants – many of which are owned by Chinese-Americans.
美国厨师安德鲁·齐默恩提出了一个关于正宗性更具争议性的观点，他声称他能以比现有餐馆（其中许多是华裔美国人开的）更地道的方式将中国菜带到明尼苏达州。
Writer and food podcaster Ruth Tam points out that while these restaurants altered their menus to suit local tastes, so does Zimmern.
作家兼美食播客主持人露丝·谭指出，虽然这些餐馆改变了菜单以适应当地口味，但齐默恩也是如此。
So, while food and identity are closely linked, and failure to respect authenticity can cause offence, could there be problems with the whole idea of authenticity?
那么，虽然食物和身份认同紧密相连，不尊重正宗性可能会引起冒犯，但整个正宗性概念本身是否存在问题呢？